<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/</link><description>Recent content in Setup | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/</guid><description>Setup Install Community Edition Try Enterprise Edition Compare Editions The setup section contains instructions for installing the Stash and its various components in Kubernetes. This section has been divided into the following sub-sections:
Install Stash: Installation instructions for Stash and its various components. Community Edition: Installation instructions for Stash Community Edition. Enterprise Edition: Installation instructions for Stash Enterprise Edition. Stash kubectl Plugin: Installation instructions for Stash kubectl plugin.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/upgrade/</guid><description>Upgrading Stash This guide will show you how to upgrade the Stash operator. Here, we are going to show how to update the license and how to upgrade between two Stash versions.
Upgrading Operator If you are using Stash v202X.X.X, you can easily upgrade to the latest version. At first, make sure that you have read the changelog of your desired version from here. Then, follow the following steps.
1. Update Operator Helm 3 Helm 2 YAML Using Helm 3</description></item></channel></rss>