<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stash MongoDB Addon on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/</link><description>Recent content in Stash MongoDB Addon on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Backup &amp; Restore MongoDB ReplicaSet Cluster | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/replicaset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/replicaset/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Backup and Restore MongoDB ReplicaSet Clusters using Stash Stash supports taking backup and restores MongoDB ReplicaSet clusters in &amp;ldquo;idiomatic&amp;rdquo; way. This guide will show you how you can backup and restore your MongoDB ReplicaSet clusters with Stash.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>Backup &amp; Restore Sharded MongoDB Cluster| Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/sharding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/sharding/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Backup and Restore MongoDB Sharded Clusters using Stash Stash 0.9.0+ supports taking backup and restores MongoDB Sharded clusters in &amp;ldquo;idiomatic&amp;rdquo; way. This guide will show you how you can backup and restore your MongoDB Sharded clusters with Stash.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>Backup &amp; Restore Standalone MongoDB | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/standalone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/standalone/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Backup and Restore MongoDB database using Stash Stash 0.9.0+ supports backup and restoration of MongoDB databases. This guide will show you how you can backup and restore your MongoDB database with Stash.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>MongoDB Addon Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Stash MongoDB Addon Stash 0.9.0+ supports extending its functionality through addons. Stash MongoDB addon enables Stash to backup and restore MongoDB databases.
This guide will give you an overview of which MongoDB versions are supported and how the docs are organized.
Supported MongoDB Versions Stash has the following addon versions for MongoDB:
3.</description></item><item><title>MongoDB Backup Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mongodb/overview/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. How Stash Backup &amp;amp; Restore MongoDB Database Stash 0.9.0+ supports backup and restore operation of many databases. This guide will give you an overview of how MongoDB database backup and restore process works in Stash.
How Backup Works The following diagram shows how Stash takes backup of a MongoDB database. Open the image in a new tab to see the enlarged version.</description></item></channel></rss>