<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stash PostgreSQL Addon on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/</link><description>Recent content in Stash PostgreSQL Addon on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PostgreSQL Addon Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Stash PostgreSQL Addon Stash 0.9.0+ supports extending its functionality through addons. Stash PostgreSQL addon enables Stash to backup and restore PostgreSQL databases.
This guide will give you an overview of which PostgreSQL versions are supported and how the docs are organized.
Supported PostgreSQL Versions Stash has the following addon versions for PostgreSQL:
10.</description></item><item><title>PostgreSQL Backup &amp; Restore Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/overview/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. How Stash Backup &amp;amp; Restore PostgreSQL Database Stash 0.9.0+ supports backup and restore operation of many databases. This guide will give you an overview of how PostgreSQL database backup and restore process works in Stash.
How Backup Works The following diagram shows how Stash takes backup of a PostgreSQL database. Open the image in a new tab to see the enlarged version.</description></item><item><title>PostgreSQL | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/auto-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/auto-backup/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Backup PostgreSQL using Stash Auto-Backup Stash can be configured to automatically backup any PostgreSQL database in your cluster. Stash enables cluster administrators to deploy backup blueprints ahead of time so that the database owners can easily backup their database with just a few annotations.
In this tutorial, we are going to show how you can configure a backup blueprint for PostgreSQL databases in your cluster and backup them with few annotations.</description></item><item><title>PostgreSQL | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/standalone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.04.12/addons/postgres/standalone/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Backup and Restore PostgreSQL database using Stash Stash 0.9.0+ supports backup and restoration of PostgreSQL databases. This guide will show you how you can backup and restore your PostgreSQL database with Stash.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>