<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stash MariaDB Addon on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/</link><description>Recent content in Stash MariaDB Addon on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Logical Backup &amp; Restore MariaDB | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/helm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/helm/</guid><description>Take a logical backup of the MariaDB database using Stash Stash v0.11.8+ supports backup and restoration of MariaDB databases. This guide will show you how you can take a logical backup of your MariaDB databases and restore them using Stash.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. Install Stash Enterprise in your cluster following the steps here.</description></item><item><title>MariaDB Addon Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Stash MariaDB Addon Stash 0.9.0+ supports extending its functionality through addons. Stash MariaDB addon enables Stash to backup and restore MariaDB databases.
This guide will give you an overview of which MariaDB versions are supported and how the docs are organized.
Supported MariaDB Versions Stash has the following addon versions for MariaDB:
10.</description></item><item><title>MariaDB Auto-Backup | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/auto-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/auto-backup/</guid><description>Backup MariaDB using Stash Auto-Backup Stash can be configured to automatically backup any MariaDB database in your cluster. Stash enables cluster administrators to deploy backup blueprints ahead of time so that the database owners can easily backup their database with just a few annotations.
In this tutorial, we are going to show how you can configure a backup blueprint for MariaDB databases in your cluster and backup them with few annotations.</description></item><item><title>MariaDB Backup &amp; Restore Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/overview/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. How Stash Backups &amp;amp; Restores MariaDB Database Stash 0.9.0+ supports backup and restore operation of many databases. This guide will give you an overview of how MariaDB database backup and restore process works in Stash.
Logical Backup Stash supports taking logical backup of MariaDB databases using mysqldump. It is the most flexible way to perform a backup and restore, and a good choice when the data size is relatively small.</description></item><item><title>MariaDB Backup Customization | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/customization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.17/addons/mariadb/customization/</guid><description>Customizing Backup and Restore Process Stash provides rich customization supports for the backup and restore process to meet the requirements of various cluster configurations. This guide will show you some examples of these customizations.
Note: YAML files used in this tutorial are stored here.
Customizing Backup Process In this section, we are going to show you how to customize the backup process. Here, we are going to show some examples of providing arguments to the backup process, running the backup process as a specific user, ignoring some indexes during the backup process, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>