<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stash MariaDB Addon on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.08/addons/mariadb/</link><description>Recent content in Stash MariaDB Addon on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.08/addons/mariadb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MariaDB Addon Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.08/addons/mariadb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.08/addons/mariadb/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Stash MariaDB Addon Stash 0.9.0+ supports extending its functionality through addons. Stash MariaDB addon enables Stash to backup and restore MariaDB databases.
This guide will give you an overview of which MariaDB versions are supported and how the docs are organized.
Supported MariaDB Versions Stash supports backup and restore of the following MariaDB versions:</description></item><item><title>MariaDB Backup &amp; Restore Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.08/addons/mariadb/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.08/addons/mariadb/overview/</guid><description>This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install Stash Enterprise Edition to try this feature. How Stash Backups &amp;amp; Restores MariaDB Database Stash 0.9.0+ supports backup and restore operation of many databases. This guide will give you an overview of how MariaDB database backup and restore process works in Stash.
Logical Backup Stash supports taking logical backup of MariaDB databases using mysqldump. It is the most flexible way to perform a backup and restore, and a good choice when the data size is relatively small.</description></item></channel></rss>