<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Monitoring | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/latest/monitoring/</link><description>Recent content in Monitoring | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/latest/monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Builtin Prometheus | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/latest/monitoring/prometheus_builtin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/latest/monitoring/prometheus_builtin/</guid><description>Monitoring Stash with builtin Prometheus This tutorial will show you how to configure builtin Prometheus scraper to monitor Stash backup and restore operations as well as the Stash operator.
To keep Prometheus resources isolated, we are going to use a separate namespace called monitoring to deploy the Prometheus server and its respective resources. Create the namespace as below if you haven&amp;rsquo;t done already.
$ kubectl create ns monitoring namespace/monitoring created Enable Monitoring in Stash At first, we have to enable Prometheus monitoring in Stash during installation.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/latest/monitoring/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/latest/monitoring/overview/</guid><description>New to Stash? Please start here.
Monitoring Stash Stash has native support for monitoring via Prometheus. You can use builtin Prometheus scraper or prometheus-operator to monitor Stash. This tutorial will show you how Prometheus monitoring works with Stash, what metrics Stash exports, and how to enable monitoring.
How Prometheus monitoring works Stash uses Prometheus PushGateway to export the metrics for backup &amp;amp; restore operations. The following diagram shows the logical structure of the Stash monitoring flow.</description></item><item><title>Prometheus Operator | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/latest/monitoring/prometheus_operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/latest/monitoring/prometheus_operator/</guid><description>Monitoring Using Prometheus Operator Prometheus Operator provides a simple and Kubernetes native way to deploy and configure a Prometheus server. This tutorial will show you how to use the Prometheus operator for monitoring Stash.
To keep Prometheus resources isolated, we are going to use a separate namespace monitoring to deploy the Prometheus operator and respective resources. Create the namespace if you haven&amp;rsquo;t created it yet,
$ kubectl create ns monitoring namespace/monitoring created Install Prometheus Stack At first, you have to install Prometheus operator in your cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>