<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/</link><description>Recent content in Setup | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/install/</guid><description>Installation Guide Stash operator can be installed via a script or as a Helm chart.
Helm 3 (Recommended) Helm 2 YAML Using Helm 3 Stash can be installed via Helm using the chart from AppsCode Charts Repository. To install the chart with the release name stash-operator:
$ helm repo add appscode https://charts.appscode.com/stable/ $ helm repo update $ helm search repo appscode/stash --version v0.9.0-rc.4 NAME CHART VERSION APP VERSION DESCRIPTION appscode/stash v0.</description></item><item><title>Table of Contents | Setup</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/</guid><description>Setup Setup contains instructions for installing the Stash and its various components in Kubernetes.
Install Stash. Installation instructions for Stash. Uninstall Stash. Instructions for uninstallating Stash. Upgrading Stash. Instructions for upgrading Stash. Developer Guide Overview. Outlines everything you need to know from setting up your dev environment to how to build and test Stash. Release process. Steps for releasing a new version of Stash.</description></item><item><title>Uninstall</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/uninstall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/uninstall/</guid><description>Uninstall Stash To uninstall Stash operator, run the following command:
Helm 3 Helm 2 YAML Using Helm 3 In Helm 3, release names are scoped to a namespace. So, provide the namespace you used to install the operator when installing.
$ helm uninstall stash-operator --namespace kube-system Using Helm 2 $ helm delete stash-operator Using YAML (with helm 3) If you prefer to not use Helm, you can generate YAMLs from Stash chart and uninstall using kubectl.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.4/setup/upgrade/</guid><description>Upgrading Stash If you are upgrading Stash to a patch release, please reapply the installation instructions. That will upgrade the operator pod to the new version and fix any RBAC issues.
Upgrading from 0.6.x to 0.7.x If you are installing via scripts, then uninstall the old version first and then reinstall the new version. If you are using Helm, follow the instructions from setup section.
Upgrading from 0.5.x to 0.6.x The format for Restic object has changed in backward incompatiable manner between 0.</description></item></channel></rss>