<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Backup and Restore Hooks | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/</link><description>Recent content in Backup and Restore Hooks | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Backup &amp; Restore Hooks | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/backup-and-restore-hooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/backup-and-restore-hooks/</guid><description>Backup &amp;amp; Restore Hooks Stash hooks let you perform some actions before and after the backup or restore process. This is particularly helpful when you want to prepare your application before backup or restore.
Here, we are going to demonstrate how you can perform different actions before and after backup and restore a MySQL database. Some of the examples might not reflect the real-world use cases but it serves the sole purpose of demonstrating what is possible.</description></item><item><title>Hooks Examples | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/configuring-hooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/configuring-hooks/</guid><description>Configuring Different Types of Hooks In this guide, we are going to discuss how to configure different types of hooks. Here, we will give some examples of different configurations.
HTTPGet httpGet hook allows sending an HTTP GET request to an HTTP server before and after the backup/restore process. The following configurable fields are available for httpGet hook.
Field Field Type Data Type Usage host Optional String Specify the name of the host where the GET request will be sent.</description></item><item><title>Hooks in Batch Backup | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/batch-backup-hooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/batch-backup-hooks/</guid><description>Hooks in Batch Backup Stash 0.9.0+ supports taking backup of multiple co-related stateful workloads using a single configuration named BackupBatch. Combining with backup hooks, this can be very powerful. For example, you can prepare your application stack before backup to ensure backup integrity or you can send a notification to a webhook (i.e. in a Slack channel via slack incoming webhook) before or after the backup of all the resources of your application stack.</description></item><item><title>Hooks Overview | Stash</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v0.9.0-rc.6/guides/latest/hooks/overview/</guid><description>Stash Backup and Restore Hooks Stash v0.9.0+ supports executing custom commands before and after backup or restore process. This is called hook in Stash. This guide will give you an overview of what kind of hooks you can execute, how the hooks get executed, and how the hooks behave in different scenarios.
Types of Hooks We can categorize Stash backup and restore hooks based on the action they perform and based on their execution order.</description></item></channel></rss>