<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Installation Guide | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/</link><description>Recent content in Installation Guide | Stash on Backup your Kubernetes Stateful Applications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install Stash Community Edition</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/community/</guid><description>Install Stash Community Edition Stash Community edition is available under AppsCode-Community-1.0.0 license and free to use for both commercial and non-commercial purposes. It comes with all the basic backup functionalities. However, it lacks some advanced features such as Database Backup, Auto-Backup, Batch Backup, and Local Backend support, etc. compared to the Enterprise edition. A full features comparison between the Stash Community edition and Enterprise edition can be found here.
To use Stash Community edition, you can grab 1 year free license from here.</description></item><item><title>Install Stash Enterprise Edition</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/enterprise/</guid><description>Install Stash Enterprise Edition Stash Enterprise edition is the open core version of Stash. It comes with all the functionalities of Stash Community edition as well as some advanced features such as Auto-Backup, Batch Backup, and Local Backend support, etc. A full features comparison between Stash Enterprise Edition and community version can be found here.
If you are willing to try Stash Enterprise Edition, you can grab a 14 days trial license from here.</description></item><item><title>Install Stash kubectl Plugin</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/kubectl_plugin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/kubectl_plugin/</guid><description>Install Stash kubectl Plugin Stash provides a kubectl plugin to interact with Stash resources. You can download the pre-build binaries from stashed/cli releases and put it into one of your installation directory denoted by $PATH variable.
Here is a simple Linux command to install the latest 64-bit Linux binary directly into your /usr/local/bin directory:
# Linux amd 64-bit wget -O kubectl-stash https://github.com/stashed/cli/releases/download/v0.11.2/kubectl-stash-linux-amd64 \ &amp;amp;&amp;amp; chmod +x kubectl-stash \ &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo mv kubectl-stash /usr/local/bin/ # Mac OSX 64-bit wget -O kubectl-stash https://github.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting Stash Installation</title><link>https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/troubleshoting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stash.run/docs/v2020.09.29/setup/install/troubleshoting/</guid><description>Installing in GKE Cluster If you are installing Stash on a GKE cluster, you will need cluster admin permissions to install Stash operator. Run the following command to grant admin permision to the cluster.
$ kubectl create clusterrolebinding &amp;#34;cluster-admin-$(whoami)&amp;#34; \ --clusterrole=cluster-admin \ --user=&amp;#34;$(gcloud config get-value core/account)&amp;#34; In addition, if your GKE cluster is a private cluster, you will need to either add an additional firewall rule that allows master nodes access port 8443/tcp on worker nodes, or change the existing rule that allows access to ports 443/tcp and 10250/tcp to also allow access to port 8443/tcp.</description></item></channel></rss>